hello youtubers
we got this fantastic billboard box
radio speaker it's not and it has radio
on it
you can listen to all functions of it
it's pretty big
we got this at the uh at ross the other
day
it's really 60 but it was 30. see here's
the back of it
i got it plugged in right now guys
this is going to blow your mind it's
going to sound really good
my wife tells me turn that off i don't
want to hear it
that's how good and loud it will be so
it's got some functions on it you got
you got speaker control you got echo
control
you got audio you put it on audio you
plug the
one jack into the audio and one to your
computer has channels
and other things in there and first
we're gonna listen to the radio one
first hold on
see it does that got this little blue
light
i could listen to radio
[Music]
i gotta change it because i don't think
how many really it's really really
really
really times thirty that's third
[Music]
but you know okay so anyway
let's i'm gonna put on auxiliary
and let you hear that i can't play music
too much because you know youtube has
her
their rules i'm gonna play a quick song
for like maybe a couple minutes
did you know that shift brings the test
drive right to you okay
all right let's turn that off see how
listen to this
and if there's a man upstairs he kept
bringing me rain
but i've been setting up prayers
that's all i can play on that you know
because you know can't play music on
there
because it's copyrighted so that's what
this uh
speaker is gonna sound like it's got
really
good sound for the money was great
um i got it in this box right here
it comes in this box billboard makes
other products like this these are
great speakers see and then i'm going to
show you
right here so you can see what exactly
is in right there
their bluetooth 29.99
and i paid and they're usually 60 i got
that at ross
see here it is and it has those
multi-colored lights in front of it
and you can do
uh led radio fm
and there's a lot of other stuff and you
can even hook a microphone in there guys
if you want to be a dj
so and that's tweeter
frequency 40 ounce
kilohertz 2.7 22
amp lithium battery so it charges up to
50 hours
it has a microphone so and a pa system
so it's a pretty
awesome great system how i got this
um these this is the two terabyte i got
at target the other day
do you know this is just this whopping
baby right here is going for
82 but i got it on sale for 58
and then i bought it uh a two-year
protection plan for eight so i came out
because i have i don't i have a lot of
storage issues on my uh
computer so this is a portable hard
drive
seagate's a pretty good name brand
company
and i got it at target so it's gonna be
a good deal i just wanted to show you
guys and let you know these product
updates and items we got
so here's another item we bought the
other day we went
to the dollar general
dollar tree and we got this stapler see
that's a
swing line that's a name brand stapler
only paid three dollars for it hopefully
it was a good staple but three dollars
for it
so that's a short vlog i hope
everybody's doing fantastic
you know with this varying going on guys
just chill have fun
go to your run down your local ross
and remember there's always bargains
like i said that
portable hard drive was only
fifty eight nine dollars fifty eight
fifty nine dollars and usually 82
so you can find some bargains go get
them
go get them while they last make sure
you put your thumbs up if you love this
video
put your thumbs down if you don't like
this video
and put your hands in the air like you
don't care and
keep watching watching and we're gonna
do some more reviews if you don't watch
then you'll miss
please subscribe and bring that
notification so you don't miss your
miss those uh upcoming product reviews
coming up
thank you have a nice one